(indistinct party chatter)
(Future's "Real Sisters"
playing)
*
ERN: Yo, I think Chris knows
we're here or something.
ALFRED: Yeah, go see him.
Get us paid,
and ask him what the fuck
is up with this.
Champagne.
We get three bottles.
Of this shit?
Naw, man, I need brown, bro,
not no...
rosé--whatever this
bubbly SpongeBob piss is.
No, no,
it's whatever, man.
You know, I get
20% of my drinks for free, so.
How so?
I'm that guy;
people see me
and they just
want to give me free drinks.
What can I say?
I'm the guy.
Mm.
Hey.
Shit.
Yeah.
(chuckling)
Hey, baby.
-The fu--
-Yo,
it's just
a club appearance, man--
Man, why I feel
like nobody care I'm here?
It--see, see, man,
that section,
over there?
That section?
That should be my section, man.
Man, who over there
more important than me, anyway?
-Shit.
-(chuckles)
If you want to stunt,
we can do that next year,
but right now, let's focus
on getting paid.
(scoffs)
Now, hold up, man.
Make sure you keep an eye
on that promoter.
I don't trust his kind, man.
He gonna try and play us.
-His kind?
-Yeah.
What is this,
The Hobbit?
"We're from
two different worlds."
Man, he-- he Nigerian, man.
I don't trust Nigerians.
Darius is Nigerian.
He is?
Yeah.
This nigga--
(groans)
Relax, man.
No, man, I don't trust
niggas in the club, man.
Yo.
Are you Paper Boi?
DARIUS: Yes.
ALFRED: Naw.
-Yeah you are.
-Then nigga, why'd you ask
if you already
know the answer then?
-Man, I love your shit, bro.
-Okay?
"Trust I'ma get these bricks
off the shelf.
Trust Paper Boi, trust no man,
I don't even trust myself."
Yeah, I know it.
Thanks, man, cool.
MAN:
"This is what it be like
"when you wake up
with that paper on you.
"Cold world, N-word snitching,
caught that lead pneumonia.
"Cold world, but a N-word,
not from North Carolina.
"I put the bricks on a boat,
make it hard to find 'em.
"I just might sling it to your
daughter for that new designer.
"This is the
realest shit I wrote,
"I never touch a liar.
"I got the clips in the
drawer dresser behind the CK.
"Got this long thing
in your face like Dekimbe.
"Got a bitch calling out my
name, oh, you thirst-ay?
"I've been
* Running the streets
* "Looking out for a real one
* I'ma move like a crook move,
but I'm God's son" *
Thank you.
All right, man.
* "I been running
the streets *
* "Looking out for
a real one *
* I'ma move like a crook move,
but I'm God's son" *
Thanks, man.
* Fuck around with me,
you tryna dodge bullets *
* Serving packs of chickens
in a Dodge Hemi *
(music muffled)
(indistinct talking)
Yo, how we feeling, Primal?
(cheers)
No, no, no, no.
How we feeling, Primal?
(cheering and whooping)
Yo, yo, yo, yo.
We got a surprise tonight.
Marcus Miles
is in the house.
Atlanta Hawks' point guard,
what's good?
(cheering and whooping)
Oh yeah, oh yeah.
And-- we got my nigga,
Paper Boi!
Paper Boi is in the house!
Make some noise!
(air horn blaring)
(smattering of applause)
(Young Dro's "We In Da City"
plays)
(beat drops)
* Car ain't got no roof
* I can't hear it, bro
* We be in da city
* All my bitches with it
* Hey, hey
* Uh-oh, where your ho at?
* We be in da city
* All my bitches with it
* Where you be at bruh?
* My crips in the city
* My bloods in the da bitty
* Guns up in Rambo house
* Blocks in dat bando house
* Choppas come from Yucatan
* You da man, you da man
* I'm sittin
up in this dually man *
* Don't make me
spray this Uzi man *
* Pop shit
you get popped quick *
* No roof this drop sick
* My crew we rock shit
* Uh-oh where your ho at?
* You heard me?
* Uh-oh she where dro at!
What?
* Car ain't got no roof
All right, cool.
* We be in da city
* All my bitches with it
(music mixes)
(trap music)
* Got smart
big head *
* Double cut
sprang *
* Good grams
kush with it *
* Had wood
sprang *
* Your chick
have respect *
* Where you know me?
Sprang *
* Pull up
jumpshot *
* Fade away
sprang *
* Sprang, sprang, sprang,
sprang, sprang, sprang sprang *
sprang, sprang *
(groans)
This shit is wack as fuck!
Ah, come on, man,
it ain't all that bad.
Why, man?
'Cause we still getting paid?
Man, fuck the club!
Could have stayed at home
and finished "Amadeus"
and had a better time, man.
(muttering)
Well, that's true.
Look, man.
Marcus Miles over there
getting all the cream, man,
hogging all the hos.
Fuck him too!
Marcus Miles
is pretty cool, man.
You know he got
that invisible car?
What?
(scoffs)
Nigga, no, he don't.
He do.
It's like a prototype,
something like--look.
Nig--
Man, that--
that shit ain't real, man.
Okay.
Look, come on, man.
Chill out, hey, look.
We can turn this thing around.
Like, uh....look.
That girl right there.
She been looking this way
all night.
All right, and I know
she ain't looking at me.
Well, how you figure
she want me though?
'Cause she would have
been notice this
creepy look
I've been giving her.
Psychology.
Well, we bout to find out.
Hey!
Hey, who want to party
with Team Paper Boi?
(cheers)
Bottles on me!
Yeah! Here!
That's what I'm saying!
Whoo-hoo!
DARIUS: Come on
to the other side.
Hello, hello, hello.
This VIP,
welcome, welcome, welcome.
(indistinct talking)
Hey, Chris.
Hey, there you go,
what happened?
I turned around,
you were gone.
Yeah, I lost you
in the crowd, man.
That's all good, man.
You want a shot?
No, I--I hate shots.
Okay, can we just finish
the financial aspect of this?
I got you.
Just let me take
these drinks to my ladies
and we'll finish up,
all right?
Follow me.
Ladies, this is Earn.
Hey, what's up?
Um.
No thanks.
No, it's cool, I'm--I'm friends
with Chris.
We don't know him, either.
I hate shots, man.
(Crime Mob's
"Knuck If You Buck" playing)
*
Oh, I--I'll be back.
Excuse me.
Coming through,
coming through.
Hey, man,
uh, can you help me out?
MAN:
No problem, player.
DARIUS:
Thank you, player.
Question.
Have you ever had to
throw out another bouncer?
Yeah.
How was it?
Hard.
-He knew all the moves.
-Hmm.
-There's the guy.
-Here I am.
Whoo.
I'm gonna go
watch people smoke.
See ya.
You on the move,
excuse me.
(muffled club music)
(toilet flushes)
Sup, Chris.
Earnest.
What happened, man?
What happened was
you slippery as fuck, Chris.
And I want my money, now.
All right, man.
Just relax.
Let me finish up.
Gonna wash your hands?
No.
Yo, what up?
I'm back.
VIP only.
-Come on, man.
-You got a wristband?
Yeah.
Yeah, right here.
-It's purple.
-So?
So to get in this section,
you need a yellow one.
Oh, well--uh--
I don't have a yellow one,
but I do have this purple one
and this red one.
I don't know
what a red one's for.
Me, neither.
I can't help you, man.
Come on, man,
you literally just
let me out of here.
Remember, we did the--
fist bump and everything
and none of that
don't mean shit to you?
Okay.
This is meaningless.
(Dreezy's "Body"
featuring Jeremih playing)
CHRIS:
Let me get a Hennessy.
You want something?
Laphroaig.
Damn.
You really going
for my pockets, huh?
I earned it.
-Thanks, honey.
-Thank you.
Cheers.
* Yo body on my body, baby
* I'm about to catch
a body in here baby *
-The fuck?
-(laughing)
I'm sorry,
but that was awesome.
You saw--you saw that, right?
-Yes.
-Fuck, he--
WOMAN:
It's hilarious.
You should see
your face right now.
(laughs)
Thank you.
Thanks--you're awesome.
Thank you for--
for being awesome.
Love it.
Relax.
You ain't got to
get so sensitive.
I hate shots.
I hate the club.
I hate...
people at the club.
I hate--
This shit is pointless,
it's like a money suck.
Can I give you
some advice?
Sure.
Leave.
No one is keeping you here.
But if you're at the club,
that means you deep down
want to be at the club.
You're not special.
To be fair,
you don't look the usual type.
What's the usual type?
That guy.
MAN:
Excuse me, sir. Sir.
You need to move up out of here.
We don't do that in here.
-Rubbing your nipples and shit.
-(laughs)
-Come on, man, get outta here.
ALFRED: Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
-So you hit his car?
-Uh, yeah.
-No--
-I had to.
So then I go back
and sit in my car...
-Uh-huh.
-And I'm crying.
-Well, fake crying.
-(laughs)
(both laugh)
And the guy comes up to me
and he's like,
(as man) "Damn, I was gonna
let you go, baby girl,
but my car's fucked up!"
Oh, no.
No--no, you know what?
-Whatever to that nigga, man.
-Whatever.
-Hey you want to get a photo?
-Mm-hmm.
-Let's get a phot--
Hey, hey!
Nigga, hey, hey, hey,
where you going, Ansel Adams?
Man, you don't want to get
a exclusive photo
of Team Paper Boi?
No, I'm good, man.
Wait.
Man, look.
You sure?
Marcus Miles got
his pet peacock here tonight.
And it's got
a leather jacket on.
That's front-page news.
Nice shoes, bro.
(shutter clicks)
(laughs)
Yeah, man.
To that nigga, man?
Whatever man.
Hell, let's--
let's toast it up, man.
-Yeah.
-Toast it up.
BARTENDER: See, he's tell them
some bullshit about
how VIP is at capacity
but he can hook them up.
See,
there are four of them,
but he says he
only has two wristbands.
See, if only two go,
they feel special.
They have a better time.
(chuckles)
Everyone needs to
feel special sometimes.
even if it's
some janky nigga
telling your two friends
they can't come in.
Why do you think porn exists?
Wow.
You were Marxist
until you got kind of sexist.
(scoffs)
Then why am--
why am I here?
Tell me that.
The same reason
everyone else is here.
To feel good
about yourself and stunt.
(imitates buzzer)
Wrong.
I'm here for work.
Exactly.
You want to make more money
to feel good about yourself
like everyone else.
And you're stunting
by playing like,
"Oh, I came here to handle
business like a boss."
No...no.
No--
Don't be an asshole.
Okay?
You asked.
(scoffs)
All right, then,
I guess I'll...
just take the check,
Tiresias.
You better tip.
Hey, Ken.
What's up, hon?
You want the regular?
Fire alarm.
(slow club music)
*
(muffled club music)
That nigga called
the cops on me.
What?
And that wasn't even
the crazy part.
-Oh, come on.
-Then he goes,
"Oh, shit, my gun,"
runs back to his car
and stashes it
in the bushes.
Damn, girl,
you wasn't scared?
Scared for what?
The cops was on their way.
I straight
told on his ass.
(laughs)
Oh, I was just gonna
top you off, big dog.
No, no, no,
I--I can top myself off, dude.
-I got you.
-I can top myself off, man!
Who the hell are you?
I'm a promoter, man.
Well, actually--actually,
I'm a rapper from Harlem,
you know.
You know A$AP Rocky?
A lil' back?
Well, I don't know
any of them, but--
I went to school with Janice.
Yeah, man.
Yo, I got--I got a CD
that's about to drop, too, man.
I got like four
followers on MySpace...
(voices blur indistinctly)
(club sounds blur indistinctly)
(glass knocks over)
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo.
He cool, man, he with me.
Nigga, who are you?
Hey.
Hey!
All you niggas,
get the fuck out
of my section!
WOMAN: Excuse me?
ALFRED:
Get up, let's go!
Hey--hey--hey,
wait--you--you, hey, come on.
Come on, not y'all,
y'all cool.
Come on back here.
(chuckles)
Okay, girl,
let's go.
'Cause Marcus Miles'
section is over there
with the bottles.
No.
No-no-no-no-no,
I'm bout to get bottles
right now.
Hey, hey!
Sweetheart!
Yeah, over here.
Ladies and gentlemen,
ladies and gentlemen,
Marcus Miles
has just bought
the entire bar tonight!
(cheers and applause)
So we will no longer
be serving drinks.
all: What?
He owns all the liquor
in the club,
and, uh,
I think he's leaving.
(crowd murmuring)
So...
(indistinct talking)
MAN:(laughs)
You broke!
(lighter clicks)
No, I could hook it up.
(R&B music over radio)
Bro, what are you doing
in here?
I want m--
I want my money.
I want my $5,000.
Oh, you mean your $750?
W--what?
Let me explain
something to you.
You know what it takes
to run a club?
The expenses?
Well, let's do some math.
We paid for the flyers.
And then your boy
exceeded his
alcohol order limit.
(gags)
And then we had to pay for
extra security
because Paper Boi's
a thug
and that's not cheap.
And then,
he was supposed to perform.
-What? No.
-Yeah.
He was supposed to perform.
So all in all,
you guys get
$750.
And that's me being nice.
Nigga, that wasn't
the deal, man--
Hey, don't start that
with me, motherfucker,
'cause I don't play that shit.
That's what I'm paying you.
Now, you better
check your tone
and get the fuck up
out of my office
before I go
get the heater.
* I don't care
No one to love me *
No one to think of me *
* I don't care
no one *
Damn, this shit lame.
(scoffs)
It ain't even
2:00 a.m. yet.
-Yeah, this is so wack.
-(chuckles)
(sighs)
But at least it wasn't
a complete loss.
I met a cool-ass nigga.
Me?
Well, hold up, okay?
Hold up, baby.
(chuckles)
(line trills)
(phone rings)
(video game playing over TV)
Yo.
Hey.
Hey, man, were you go?
We leaving.
Yo, I'm already
at the crib, bro.
ALFRED: What?
-Mm-hmm.
They said I had on the wrong
color wristband
or something.
Now I'm on this Zoo Tycoon.
Nigerians.
Hey, hey, Janice--hey.
Hey, man, let me call you back,
all right?
DARIUS: Yep.
(slurps)
Hey.
Hey-hey-hey-hey-hey-hey, baby.
Hey, wait,
wait-wait-wait-wait-wait.
Let's exchange information
or something.
Yeah.
You can follow me on Instagram.
Come on.
Well, I have a boyfriend.
(laughs)
Wait, what?
Oh.
That's so sweet.
I'm for real gonna check out
your music on SoundCloud.
Come on.
Are you serious?
(sighs)
A boyfriend?
So you been wasting my time
this entire night then?
Wasting your time?
Wait--
we had a good time, right?
That's why you came here.
To party with cute girls
like me and have a good time.
We did that.
Yo, what the fuck!
(groans)
Hey--hey, man.
Hey, where you been?
Look, we need to get out
of this club before I
punch somebody in the face.
Man, you get our money?
Earn.
Man, he fucked us, man,
like he--
he only gave us $750, man.
I'm sorry, man--
I just don't scare people
like you, man.
Like, niggas know
I drink juice and shit.
Fuck that!
We getting our
fucking money, man.
What's up, Earn?
Nigga, what's up, Swiff,
what are you doing here?
You know sweaty-ass Tony,
it's that nigga birthday man.
Ah, no, nigga ah--
let's go!
(Baby Huey's "Hard Times"
plays)
Okay, this nigga in my ear.
-Just follow, just follow.
-Oh shit.
* Cold, cold eyes
upon me they stare *
* People all around me
and they're all in fear *
* They don't seem to want me
but they won't admit *
* I must be some kind of--
(screams)
Where my money, nigga?
-Man, I gave Earn your money.
-Damn!
Where's my fucking
money, man?
Please!
I can write you a check.
Nigga, do I look like a bank?
I don't take fucking checks!
Oh!
(indistinct shouts)
(all shouting)
Where's my money at?
I got it all right here, man.
Just take it, just take it.
Shit.
This is gangsta.
Yeah, nigga.
(slap lands)
Oh!
Shit!
Damn!
-Hey, yo.
-Come on, man.
We got to dip now.
Hey, man,
you should really
practice better
business habits.
-Have a good night.
-Really man?
Oh, my God.
You all right?
(pants)
That boy's gonna be a star.
Man--call the police!
He talked to you
like, don't--
"I don't take checks."
-No, wilin-ass looking nigga.
-I don't take checks.
(both laugh)
Yo, dude,
I thought he was gonna die.
I told you
I don't like the club, bro.
-Yo, we just like...
-I mean.
-Shit was fire, man.
-(chuckles)
We should get some food, though,
man, let's get out of here.
-No, man, I'm so hungry.
-I know.
I want like, a,
a waffle and like
a chicken sausage so bad.
What you gonna do
with that chicken sausage?
-Tear it up, man.
-Tear it up.
-That's some gay-ass shit.
-Man, I'll--
-I'll gobble it.
- Chicken sausage. (laughs)
Gobble it,
swallow the whole thing, man.
Shit, man.
(indistinct shouts)
Man--oh, this nigga's
getting in here?
The fuck is happening?
-Hey!
-Oh, damn.
(gunfire)
Oh, shit!
(people screaming
Go, Earn, man!
Go, go, go, go!
(tires screech)
(engine revving)
-(laughs)
-Oh, my God.
-Yo, that shit was so crazy.
-Yo, man.
I heard them gunshots
and I just went into
survival mode, boy.
-I was like--
-Yeah, I bet you did.
Yo, you see that man?
Man, he just blew
that dude's brains out.
Wait, wait,
so that was Marcus Miles?
both: No, no.
-Man...
-Well, who was it?
Wait, I missing it.
Who was it? Was it Marcus--
Oh!
Oh, ow, it's so hot.
-It's so hot.
-Be careful, man.
(laughs)
MALE REPORTER ON TV:
Tonight on Channel 5 News,
a man was shot
in an altercation
at local area nightclub,
Primal.
And popular Atlanta rapper
Paper Boi
is wanted for questioning
about an armed robbery
at the same establishment.
(news theme music)
MALE REPORTER:
A new health and wellness study
finds that perpetual optimists
like to think that their
-cheery disposition--
-Fuck the club.
(Little Beaver's
"I Can Dig It, Baby" plays)
*
* Whoo-hoo
* Hey, babe
* You say you want to go out
* And have yourself
a little fun *
* Well, I can dig it, baby
*
* You say you want
to hang out *
* To find out
what life's all about *
* Oh, I can dig it, baby
*
* Hey, babe
* I know you're doing me
wrong *
* But I've been hanging on
* Just playing along
* Oh, I can dig it, baby, yeah